<resources>
    <string name="app_name">30 Day to a Better You</string>

    <string name="topic1">Glimps of Android Development</string>
    <string name="desctopic1">Define your goals for becoming an Android developer. What kind of apps do you want to build? What areas do you want to specialize in? Research the career path and understand the skills required.</string>
    <string name="topic2">Android Dev. Environment Setup</string>
    <string name="desctopic2">Download and install Android Studio (the official IDE for Android development) and set up your development environment. Explore the layout and basic functionalities of Android Studio.</string>
    <string name="topic3">Java the Father</string>
    <string name="desctopic3"> If you\'re new to programming, spend these days learning the fundamentals of Java programming. Focus on variables, data types, operators, control flow statements, and object-oriented programming concepts like classes, objects, inheritance, and polymorphism.</string>
    <string name="topic4">Android Dev. Intro 1</string>
    <string name="desctopic4">Get familiar with the basic building blocks of Android apps: Activities, Layouts, Views, and Resources. Understand the Activity Lifecycle and how it manages different app states.</string>
    <string name="topic5">Android Dev. Intro 2</string>
    <string name="desctopic5">More complex and deeper about Get familiar with the basic building blocks of Android apps: Activities, Layouts, Views, and Resources. Understand the Activity Lifecycle and how it manages different app states.</string>
    <string name="topic6">Layouting 101</string>
    <string name="desctopic6">Learn how to design user interfaces (UI) in Android using XML. Explore different types of layouts (linear, relative, etc.) and views (buttons, text fields, images, etc.).</string>
    <string name="topic7">Layouting 101 pt.2</string>
    <string name="desctopic7">Glimps of the jetpack compose</string>
    <string name="topic8">Working with Resources</string>
    <string name="desctopic8">Understand the different types of resources used in Android development (strings, images, styles, colors, etc.) and how to manage them within your project.</string>
    <string name="topic9">Deep dive about Resource</string>
    <string name="desctopic9">More about understanding the different types of resources used in Android development (strings, images, styles, colors, etc.) and how to manage them within your project.</string>
    <string name="topic10">First App</string>
    <string name="desctopic10">Start developing a simple app like a Tip Counter app or a Basic Calculator.</string>
    <string name="topic11">Java Collections and Exceptions</string>
    <string name="desctopic11">Explore more advanced Java topics like collections and exceptions, </string>
    <string name="topic12">Java Threads</string>
    <string name="desctopic12"> Explore more advanced Java topics like collections, exceptions, threads, and networking basics. These concepts will be crucial for building more complex applications.</string>
    <string name="topic13">Jaca Networking Basic</string>
    <string name="desctopic13"> Explore advanced Java about networking basics. These concepts will be crucial for building more complex applications.</string>
    <string name="topic14">Meet Kotlin</string>
    <string name="desctopic14">Learn about Kotlin, a modern programming language increasingly used for Android development. </string>
    <string name="topic15">Kotlin for Android Dev.</string>
    <string name="desctopic15">Understand its benefits over Java and start practicing basic Kotlin syntax. </string>
    <string name="topic16">Working with Data</string>
    <string name="desctopic16">Learn how to store and manage data in Android applications. Explore SQLite databases.</string>
    <string name="topic17">Shared Preferences</string>
    <string name="desctopic17">Learn how to store and manage data in Android applications using  SharedPreferences and APIs for accessing external data sources.</string>
    <string name="topic18">in App-User Interaction</string>
    <string name="desctopic18">Understand how users interact with your app and how to handle events like button clicks, touch gestures, and sensor input.</string>
    <string name="topic19">Events</string>
    <string name="desctopic19">Using Event on your app</string>
    <string name="topic20">Your Application pt. 2</string>
    <string name="desctopic20">Apply your learnings to create a slightly more complex app with features like user input, data storage, and basic UI interactions.</string>
    <string name="topic21">Find a beauty on Material Design</string>
    <string name="desctopic21">Learn about Material Design, a design language from Google that promotes consistent and beautiful user interfaces. Apply these principles to your app design.</string>
    <string name="topic22">Material Design Principles</string>
    <string name="desctopic22">The next step of creating UI in android</string>
    <string name="topic23">Working with Git</string>
    <string name="desctopic23">Git for collaboration</string>
    <string name="topic24">Version control with Git</string>
    <string name="desctopic24">Learn Git, a version control system to track changes in your codebase and collaborate with others.</string>
    <string name="topic25">Testing your App</string>
    <string name="desctopic25">Understand the importance of testing in software development. Explore unit testing frameworks like JUnit to ensure your code functions as expected.</string>
    <string name="topic26">Testing your App pt.2</string>
    <string name="desctopic26">The comprehensive way to test an app</string>
    <string name="topic27">Android App. Deployment</string>
    <string name="desctopic27">Make your app accessible for everyone</string>
    <string name="topic28">Deploy Our App</string>
    <string name="desctopic28"> Learn how to prepare your app for release on the Google Play Store. Understand signing certificates, app bundles, and the publishing process.</string>
    <string name="topic29">Android Advance Topic</string>
    <string name="desctopic29">Look forward the unlimited journey of android dev.</string>
    <string name="topic30">Continuous Learning and Improvement enhancement</string>
    <string name="desctopic30">Becoming a great developer is a lifelong journey. Explore advanced topics like animations, custom views, services, background tasks, and different app architectures. Look for open-source projects to contribute to or build your own app idea.</string>

    <string name="topbar_android">30 Day journey of Android</string>
    <string name="btn_expand_item">See more or less info of android</string>
</resources>